A Guide to the Stanford Moore papers, Rockefeller University Faculty FA111
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Subject Files, 1974-1976; 4
  - 1980 NIH Grant Applications (Box 48, Folder 360, Folder 361, Folder 362)
  - 2', 3'-Cyclic Nucleotidase (Box 48, Folder 363)
  - Accounting (Box 48, Folder 364)
  - Acetylcholinesterase (Box 48, Folder 365)
  - Actin (Box 48, Folder 366)
  - Adriamycin (Box 48, Folder 367)
  - Affinity Chromatography (Box 49, Folder 368)
  - Aging (Box 49, Folder 369)
  - Allen Foundation (Box 49, Folder 370)
  - Alpha (Therapeutic Corporation) (Box 49, Folder 371)
  - AMF Specialty Materials Group (Box 49, Folder 372)
  - Amino Acids (Box 49, Folder 374, Folder 373)
  - Aminoacidurias (Box 49, Folder 375)
  - Aminopeptidase P, M, O (Box 49, Folder 376)
  - Animal House (Box 49, Folder 377)
  - Antibiotics (Box 49, Folder 378)
  - Apparatus (Box 49, Folder 379)
  - Arginases (Box 49, Folder 380)
  - Arteriosclerosis Committee (Box 49, Folder 381)
  - Automatic Subject Citation Alert (ASCA) (Box 50, Folder 383, Folder 382)
  - Aspartame (Box 50, Folder 384)
  - Atlas of Protein Sequence and Structure, 1976 (Box 50, Folder 385)
  - Atlas of Protein Structure (Box 50, Folder 386, Folder 386A)
    Folder 386A is restricted.
  - Available Biochemists (Box 50, Folder 387)
  - Atomic Energy (Box 51, Folder 388)
  - Atomic Models (Box 51, Folder 389)
  - Autolab (Box 51, Folder 390)
  - Automatic Fraction Collection (Box 51, Folder 391, Folder 392)
  - Available Biochemists (Box 51, Folder 393)
  - Barworth, Inc. (Box 51, Folder 394)
  - Belgian Royal Academy (Box 51, Folder 395)
  - Bile Salts (Box 51, Folder 396)
  - Biochemical Engineering (Box 52, Folder 397)
  - Biochemical Positions Open (Box 52, Folder 398)
  - Biochemical Society (Box 52, Folder 399)
  - Biochemistry Journals and "Nature" (Box 52, Folder 400)
  - Bioenergetics (Box 52, Folder 401)
  - Biomed Instruments (Box 52, Folder 402)
  - Biosis (Box 52, Folder 403)
  - Peter Blackburn (Box 53, Folder 405, Box 52, Folder 404A, Folder 404)
    Folder 404A is restricted
  - Blackburn - National Science Foundation (Box 53, Folder 406)
  - Blood (Box 53, Folder 407)
  - Blood and Urine (Box 53, Folder 408)
  - Bombardier Beetle and Filipino Snail (Box 53, Folder 409)
  - Books (Box 54, Folder 411, Box 53, Folder 410)
  - Brain Chemistry (Box 54, Folder 412)
  - Brain Information Service (Box 54, Folder 413)
  - Brain Proteins (Box 54, Folder 414)
  - Brochures (Box 54, Folder 415)
  - Buffers (Box 54, Folder 417)
  - Calculators (Box 54, Folder 418)
  - Calibiochem (Box 54, Folder 419)
  - Cancer (Box 54, Folder 420)
  - Carbohydrate Analysis (Box 55, Folder 421)
  - Carbohydrates (Box 55, Folder 423, Folder 422)
  - γ-Carboxyglutamic Acid (Box 55, Folder 424)
  - Carboxylic Acid (Box 55, Folder 425)
  - Carboxypeptidase Y (Box 55, Folder 426)
  - Carlsberg Laboratory (Box 56, Folder 433, Box 55, Folder 427, Folder 429, Folder 430, Folder 431, Folder 432, Folder 428)
  - Carrier Foundation (Box 56, Folder 434, Box 57, Folder 434A)
    Folder 434A is restricted
  - Cassava (Box 57, Folder 435)
  - Cell Biology (Box 57, Folder 437)
  - Chaire Francqui (Box 57, Folder 438)
  - Chemical Corps (Box 57, Folder 439)
  - Chemical Warfare (Box 57, Folder 440)
  - China (Box 57, Folder 441, Folder 442)
  - Chinese Typewriters (Box 57, Folder 443)
  - Cholic Acid (Box 57, Folder 444)
  - Chromatin (Box 57, Folder 445)
  - Chromatography (Box 57, Folder 446)
  - Chromatography - Procedures (Box 57, Folder 447)
  - Chromatronix (Box 57, Folder 448)
  - Circular Dichroism Studies (Box 57, Folder 449)
  - Cleavage of Peptides (Box 57, Folder 450)
  - CNRS [Centre National de la Recherche Scientifique] (Box 57, Folder 451)
  - Column Chromatography (Box 58, Folder 452, Folder 453)
  - Committees (Re: Bruce Erickson) (Box 58, Folder 454)
  - Computers (Box 58, Folder 455)
  - Congressional Records (Box 58, Folder 456)
  - Contract, Streptococcal Proteinase (Box 59, Folder 458, Box 58, Folder 457A, Folder 457)
    Folder 457A is restricted
  - Contract, Streptococcal Proteinase, Renewal (Box 59, Folder 459)
  - Council for Chemical Research (Box 59, Folder 460)
  - Counter-Current Distribution (Box 59, Folder 461)
  - Lyman C. Craig (Box 59, Folder 463, Folder 462)
  - Cross-Linking (Box 59, Folder 464)
  - Current Applications for Positions (Box 59, Folder 465)
  - Cyclic AMP (Box 60, Folder 466)
  - Cystine Method (Box 60, Folder 467)
  - Cytochromes (Box 60, Folder 468)
  - D-Amino Acids (Box 60, Folder 469)
  - James E. Darnell, Jr. (Box 60, Folder 470)
  - Deoxyribonuclease (Box 60, Folder 471)
  - Detergents (Box 60, Folder 472)
  - Dialysis (Box 60, Folder 473)
  - Richard Dickerson (Box 60, Folder 474)
  - Diketopiperazines (Box 60, Folder 475)
  - Dimethyl Sulfoxide (DMSO) (Box 60, Folder 476)
  - DNA Recombination (Box 60, Folder 477)
  - Dowex 50 Chromatography (Box 61, Folder 478)
  - Dreyfus Foundation (Box 61, Folder 479)
  - Du Pont (Box 61, Folder 480)
  - Edman Degradation (Box 61, Folder 481, Folder 483, Folder 482, Folder 484)
  - Education (Box 62, Folder 485)
  - Electrodes (Box 62, Folder 486)
  - Electronics Shop (Box 62, Folder 487)
  - Electrophoresis (Box 62, Folder 489, Folder 488)
  - End-Group Methods (Box 62, Folder 490)
  - Endorphins and Exorphins (Box 62, Folder 491)
  - Energy (Box 62, Folder 492)
  - Energy Audit (Box 62, Folder 493)
  - Engenics (Box 62, Folder 494)
  - Environment (Box 62, Folder 495)
  - Enzo (Biochem, Inc.) (Box 62, Folder 496)
  - Enzymes (Box 62, Folder 497, Box 63, Folder 498)
  - Equipment and Purchases (Box 63, Folder 499)
  - Esso Research and Engineering Company (Box 63, Folder 500)
  - Ethics (Box 63, Folder 501)
  - Exonucleases (Box 63, Folder 502)
  - Experimental Medicine Discussion Group (Box 63, Folder 503)
  - Eye (Box 63, Folder 504)
  - Fairleigh Dickinson University (Box 63, Folder 505)
  - Filters-Interference (Box 63, Folder 506)
  - Fisher (Scientific Company) (Box 63, Folder 507)
  - Fluorescamine and o-Phthalaldehyde (Box 63, Folder 508)
  - Ford Foundation (Box 64, Folder 509)
  - Funding for Research (Box 64, Folder 510, Folder 511)
  - William Fuss, Inc., Florist (Box 64, Folder 512)
  - Gas Chromatography (Box 64, Folder 515, Folder 514, Folder 513)
  - Gel Electrophoresis (Box 64, Folder 516)
  - Genetic Engineering (Box 65, Folder 517)
  - Genetics (Box 65, Folder 518)
  - Gibbs Committee (Box 65, Folder 520, Folder 519)
  - Glutathione (Box 65, Folder 521)
  - Glycoproteins (Box 65, Folder 522)
  - Graduate Students (Box 66, Folder 525)
  - Gramicidin (Box 66, Folder 526)
  - Graphic Services (Box 66, Folder 527)
  - Paul B. Hamilton (Box 66, Folder 528)
  - Philip Handler (Box 66, Folder 529)
  - Robert A. Harte (Box 66, Folder 530)
  - Hemoglobins (Box 67, Folder 531, Folder 532)
  - Hereditary Disease Foundation (HDF) (Box 67, Folder 533)
  - Histamine (Box 67, Folder 534)
  - Histidine Decarboxylase (Box 67, Folder 535)
  - Histones (Box 67, Folder 536)
  - History of Biochemistry (Box 67, Folder 537)
  - Hoefer (Scientific Instruments) (Box 67, Folder 538)
  - Homocysteine (Box 67, Folder 539)
  - Hotchkiss (Box 67, Folder 540)
  - Hotels (Box 67, Folder 541)
  - Housing (Box 67, Folder 542)
  - HPLC for Amino Acids (Box 67, Folder 543)
  - Hypoglycin A (Box 67, Folder 544)
  - Immobilized Enzymes (Box 68, Folder 545)
  - Immunology (Box 68, Folder 546)
  - Indexing (Box 68, Folder 547)
  - Information Systems (Box 68, Folder 548)
  - Infotronics Integrators (Box 68, Folder 549)
  - Insulin (Box 68, Folder 550)
  - Interferon (Box 68, Folder 551)
  - International Policy (Box 69, Folder 552)
  - Ion Exchange (Box 70, Folder 556, Box 69, Folder 555, Folder 554, Folder 553)
  - Irma T. Hirschl Charitable Trust (Box 70, Folder 557)
  - ISI [Institute for Scientific Information] (Box 70, Folder 558)
  - Isoelectric Focusing (Box 70, Folder 559)
  - Isotopes (Box 70, Folder 560)
  - IUB [International Union of Biochemistry] (Box 70, Folder 561)
  - Journal of Biological Chemistry, Ad Hoc Committee (Box 70, Folder 562)
  - Kinetics (Box 70, Folder 563)
  - Donald M. Kirschembaum (Box 70, Folder 564)
  - Koshland (Box 70, Folder 565)
  - Moses Kunitz (Box 71, Folder 566)
  - Laboratory Cleaning (Box 71, Folder 567)
  - Lamps (Box 71, Folder 568)
  - Joshua Lederberg (Box 71, Folder 569)
  - Leukemia (Box 71, Folder 570)
  - Library (Box 71, Folder 571)
  - Lilly Research Laboratories (Box 71, Folder 572)
  - Liposomes (Box 71, Folder 573)
  - Liquid Chromatography (Box 71, Folder 574)
  - Liquid Membranes (Box 71, Folder 575)
  - Liver (Box 71, Folder 576)
  - Liver Function Tests (Box 71, Folder 577)
  - Lysosomes (Box 71, Folder 578)
  - Lysozyme (Box 71, Folder 579)
  - McGraw-Hill (Box 71, Folder 580)
  - Thomas McGinnity (Box 71, Folder 581)
  - Miss McKenzie - Grants (Box 72, Folder 582A, Folder 582)
    Folder 582A is restricted
  - Malaria (Box 72, Folder 583)
  - Manhattan House (Box 72, Folder 584)
  - James M. Manning (Box 73, Folder 588, Folder 587A, Folder 590, Folder 589, Box 72, Folder 586, Folder 585, Folder 587)
    Folder 587A is restricted
  - Mathematics of Distribution (Box 73, Folder 591)
  - Mass Spectrometry (Box 74, Folder 592)
  - Membranes (Box 74, Folder 593)
  - Memory (Box 74, Folder 594)
  - Merck (Box 74, Folder 595)
  - Metabolism (Box 74, Folder 596)
  - Methadone (Box 74, Folder 597)
  - Methods - Protein Chemistry (Box 74, Folder 598)
  - Mexico (Box 74, Folder 599)
  - Micro Equipment (Box 74, Folder 600)
  - Micro Filtration Services (Box 74, Folder 601)
  - Micro Switches (Box 74, Folder 602)
  - Microchemistry (Box 74, Folder 603)
  - Microfilm (Box 74, Folder 604)
  - Microscopes (Box 74, Folder 606)
  - Mustard Gas (Box 75, Folder 607)
  - National Academy of Sciences (Box 75, Folder 608, Folder 610, Folder 609)
  - National Library of Medicine (Box 75, Folder 611)
  - National Research Council Committee on Growth (Box 75, Folder 612)
  - National Science Foundation (Box 75, Folder 613)
  - Nester-Faust (Box 75, Folder 614)
  - Neurochemistry (Box 76, Folder 615, Folder 616)
  - New England Enzyme Center (Box 77, Folder 619, Box 76, Folder 618A, Folder 618, Folder 617)
    Folder 618A is restricted
  - Nuclear Magnetic Resonance Spectrometer (NMR) (Box 77, Folder 620)
  - Rodney Nichols (Box 77, Folder 621)
  - Nichols - Neurochemistry (Box 77, Folder 622)
  - Ninhydrin (Box 78, Folder 626, Box 77, Folder 623, Folder 624, Folder 625)
  - Nucleic Acids (Box 78, Folder 627)
  - Nucleic Acids and Nucleotides (Box 78, Folder 628)
  - Nutrition (Box 78, Folder 629)
  - Oak Ridge National Laboratory (Box 79, Folder 630)
  - Office of Scientific Research and Development Circulars (Box 79, Folder 631)
  - Office of Technology Assessment (Box 79, Folder 632)
  - Organic Chemistry (Box 79, Folder 633)
  - Organic Chemistry Seminars (Box 79, Folder 634)
  - Organon (Box 79, Folder 635)
  - Page-Turners (Box 79, Folder 636)
  - Painting (Box 79, Folder 637)
  - Pancreas (Box 79, Folder 639, Folder 638)
  - Patent Policy (Box 79, Folder 640)
  - Peabody Demonstration School (Box 80, Folder 641)
  - Penicillamine (Box 80, Folder 642)
  - Pepsin (Box 80, Folder 643, Folder 644)
  - Peptide Chromatography (Box 81, Folder 645)
  - Peptide Synthesis (Box 81, Folder 646)
  - Peptides (Box 81, Folder 647)
  - Peptides and Mental Disease (Box 81, Folder 648)
  - Periodate (Box 81, Folder 649)
  - Peyton Rous Centennial (Box 81, Folder 650)
  - Pharmacology (Box 81, Folder 651)
  - Philosophy of Science (Box 81, Folder 652)
  - o-Phthalaldehyde (Box 81, Folder 653)
  - Physics (Box 81, Folder 654)
  - Placenta (Box 81, Folder 655)
  - Poland (Box 81, Folder 656)
  - Population Council (Box 82, Drawer 658, Box 81, Folder 657)
  - Population Council Vaccine (Box 82, Folder 659)
  - Porous Glass (Box 82, Folder 660)
  - Position Candidates, 1974 (Box 82, Folder 661)
  - Principles of Research (Box 82, Folder 662)
  - Prostaglandins (Box 82, Folder 663)
  - Protein Chromatography (Box 82, Folder 664)
  - Protein Modification (Box 83, Folder 665)
  - Public Health Service Grant (Box 83, Folder 667A, Folder 667)
    Folder 667A is restricted
  - Pumps (Box 83, Folder 669, Folder 668)
  - Qualifying Exams (Box 83, Folder 670)
  - Quotations and Reflections (Box 83, Folder 671)
  - Radiation Safety (Box 84, Folder 672)
  - Radioactive Isotopes (Box 84, Folder 673)
  - Radioactive Labeling (Box 84, Folder 674)
  - Radiomatic Instruments and Chemical Company (Box 84, Folder 675)
  - Reaction Mechanisms (Box 84, Folder 676)
  - Receptors (Box 84, Folder 677)
  - Recorder (Box 84, Folder 678, Box 85, Folder 682, Folder 681, Folder 680, Folder 679, Folder 686, Folder 685, Folder 684, Folder 683)
  - Recombinant DNA (Box 85, Folder 687)
  - Reproductive Biology Grant (Box 85, Folder 689, Folder 689A, Box 86, Folder 690)
  - Research Profiles (Box 86, Folder 691)
  - "Research Resources Reporter" (Box 86, Folder 692)
  - Reviews (Box 86, Folder 693)
  - Rhodopsin (Box 86, Folder 694)
  - Ribonuclease (Box 87, Folder 698, Folder 699, Box 86, Folder 696, Folder 697, Box 88, Folder 702, Folder 695, Folder 700, Folder 701)
  - Ribonuclease and Cancer (Box 88, Folder 703)
  - Ribonuclease H (Box 88, Folder 704)
  - Ribonuclease Inhibitor (Box 88, Folder 705)
  - Ribonuclease - Seminal (Box 88, Folder 706)
  - Ribosomes (Box 88, Folder 707)
  - Richards Medal (Box 88, Folder 708)
  - Richards Medal Award (Box 88, Folder 709)
  - Riverside Productions (Box 88, Folder 710)
  - Roche Institute (Box 88, Folder 711)
  - Rockefeller Foundation (Box 88, Folder 712)
  - Rockefeller University Board (Box 89, Folder 713)
  - Rockefeller University: China-Watchers (Box 89, Folder 714)
  - Rockefeller University Senate (Box 89, Folder 715)
  - Russian (Box 89, Folder 717, Folder 718, Box 90, Folder 719, Folder 716)
  - Russian Delegates (Box 90, Folder 720)
  - Savant (Box 90, Folder 721)
  - Scientia (Box 90, Folder 722)
  - Schizophrenia (Box 90, Folder 723)
  - Schoeffel (Instruments) (Box 90, Folder 724)
  - Seminar on Biochemical Methods (Box 90, Folder 726)
  - Sephadex (Box 91, Folder 728, Box 90, Folder 727)
  - Sequential Degradations (Box 91, Folder 729)
  - Serva (Box 91, Folder 730)
  - Sickle Cell Anemia (Box 91, Folder 731)
  - Sloan-Kettering (Box 91, Folder 732)
  - Soltec (Box 91, Folder 733)
  - Solubility Product Method (Box 91, Folder 734)
  - Solvents (Box 91, Folder 735)
  - Sorensen Products (Box 91, Folder 736)
  - Spectra-Physics (Box 91, Folder 737)
  - Stainless Steel (Box 91, Folder 738)
  - Stamps (Box 91, Folder 739)
  - Stationary (Box 91, Folder 740)
  - Stein Columbia Symposium (Box 91, Folder 741)
  - William H. Stein National Academy of Medicine Memoir (Box 92, Folder 742)
  - William H. Stein Obituary (Box 92, Folder 743)
  - Strepogenin (Box 92, Folder 744)
  - Students (Box 92, Folder 745, Folder 746)
  - Sulfamide (Box 92, Folder 747)
  - Suspense File (Box 92, Folder 748)
  - Sweden (Box 93, Folder 749)
  - Taurine (Box 93, Folder 750)
  - Technicon (Box 93, Folder 751, Folder 752)
  - Telephones (Box 93, Folder 753)
  - Thermometers (Box 93, Folder 754)
  - Thin-Layer [Chromatography] (Box 93, Folder 755)
  - Tower Building (Box 93, Folder 756)
  - Travel (Box 93, Folder 757)
  - Tribute to Stanford Moore (Box 93, Folder 758)
  - Tube Fittings (Box 93, Folder 759)
  - Tubercle Bacillus (Box 93, Folder 760)
  - Tyre (Box 93, Folder 761)
  - Tyrosine Phosphate (Box 94, Folder 762)
  - Ultracentrifugation (Box 94, Folder 763)
  - Ultra-Filtration (Box 94, Folder 764)
  - Union Carbide (Box 94, Folder 765)
  - Uppsala University (Box 94, Folder 766)
  - Uremia (Box 94, Folder 767)
  - Urine (Box 94, Folder 768)
  - U.V. Recording (Box 94, Folder 769)
  - Valves (Box 95, Folder 770)
  - Vanderbilt (Box 95, Folder 771)
  - Vanderbilt University Centennial Program (Box 95, Folder 772)
  - Versene (Box 95, Folder 773)
  - Vitamins (Box 95, Folder 774)
  - Vivonex (Box 95, Folder 775)
  - Water Resources (Box 95, Folder 776)
  - Waters Associates (Box 95, Folder 777)
  - Bernard Witkop (Box 95, Folder 778)
  - Worthington (Box 95, Folder 779)
  - Paul C. Zamecnik (Box 95, Folder 780)
- Lectures and Speeches, 1947-1981; 5
  Series 5, Lectures and Speeches, is arranged chronologically by year.
  Series 5, Lectures and Speeches, contains speeches and lectures given by Moore. The files typically contain notes and text written by Stanford Moore.
  - Lecture Notes (Box 96, Folder 781)
  - Staff Meetings, 1947-1949 (Box 96, Folder 782)
  - Atlantic City, 1948 (Box 96, Folder 783)
  - Harvard Seminar, 1948 (Box 96, Folder 784)
  - Cold Spring Harbor, 1949 (Box 96, Folder 785)
  - Belgium, 1950 (Box 96, Folder 786)
  - Chicago Lecture, 1950 (Box 96, Folder 787)
  - Cleveland Lectures, 1950 (Box 96, Folder 788)
  - Visiting Professorship, Francqui Chair, Brussels, 1950-1951 (Box 96, Folder 789)
  - Cornell Seminar, 1954 (Box 96, Folder 790)
  - Staff Meeting, 1954 (Box 96, Folder 791)
  - Marseille, 1955 (Box 96, Folder 792)
  - Staff Meeting, Ribonuclease, 1959 (Box 96, Folder 793)
  - Northwestern, 1960 (Box 96, Folder 794)
  - American Chemical Society, Chicago, 1961 (Box 97, Folder 795)
  - Chromatography, 1961 (Box 97, Folder 796)
  - Students, "The Isolation of Proteins", 1961 (Box 97, Folder 797)
  - Students, "Determination of the Chemical Structure of Proteins", 1961 (Box 97, Folder 798)
  - Students, "Ion Exchange Chromatography", 1961 (Box 97, Folder 799)
  - Students, "The Chemical Properties of Nucleic Acids", 1961 (Box 97, Folder 800)
  - Students, "The Three Dimensional Structures of Proteins and Nucleic Acids", 1961 (Box 97, Folder 801)
  - Christmas Lectures, 1961-1962 (Box 97, Folder 802)
  - Boston Holiday Lecture Series, 1962 (Box 97, Folder 803)
  - Seminar, 1962 (Box 97, Folder 804)
  - Students, "Determination of the Chemical Structure of Proteins", 1962 (Box 97, Folder 805)
  - Students, "Correlations Between Chemical Structure and Enzymatic Activity", 1962 (Box 97, Folder 806)
  - Students, "Nucleic Acids", 1962 (Box 97, Folder 807)
  - Japan and Israel, 1963 (Box 97, Folder 808)
  - Madras, 1963 (Box 98, Folder 809)
  - Paris, 1964 (Box 98, Folder 810)
  - Brussels, 1965 (Box 98, Folder 811)
  - Commonwealth Scientific and Industrial Research Organisation (CSIRO), 1965 (Box 98, Folder 812)
  - Paris, 1965 (Box 98, Folder 813)
  - Third International Wool Textile Research Conference, 1965 (Box 98, Folder 814)
  - Cambridge, England, 1966 (Box 98, Folder 815)
  - Demonstration for the American Association for the Advancement of Science, 1967 (Box 98, Folder 816)
  - Tokyo, 1967 (Box 98, Folder 817)
  - Michigan/Oklahoma, 1968 (Box 98, Folder 818)
  - Vanderbilt, 1968 (Box 98, Folder 819)
  - Copenhagen, 1969 (Box 98, Folder 820)
  - Marseille, 1969 (Box 98, Folder 821)
  - Padua, Canada, and Cambridge, 1969 (Box 99, Folder 822)
  - Lectures, 1970 (Box 99, Folder 823)
  - Lectures, 1971 (Box 99, Folder 824)
  - Lectures, 1972 (Box 99, Folder 825)
  - Linderstrøm-Lang Address, 1972 (Box 99, Folder 826)
  - Lectures, 1973 (Box 99, Folder 828, Folder 827)
  - Lectures, 1974 (Box 100, Folder 829)
  - Italy and England, 1975 (Box 100, Folder 830)
  - Lectures, 1975 (Box 100, Folder 831)
  - Lectures, 1976 (Box 100, Folder 832, Box 101, Folder 833)
  - Lectures, 1977 (Box 101, Folder 834, Folder 835)
  - Lectures, 1978 (Box 101, Folder 836)
  - Lectures, 1979 (Box 102, Folder 837)
  - Christmas Lectures, 1980 (Box 102, Folder 838)
  - Lectures, 1980 (Box 102, Folder 839)
  - Stein Memorial Lecture, 1981 (Box 102, Folder 840)
- Professional Travel and Activities, 1945-1982; 6
  Series 6, Professional Travel and Activites, is arranged chronologically by year.
  Series 6, Professional Travel and Activities, contains Moore's files on trips that he took which were of a professional nature, either within the United States or abroad. This series also contains files pertaining to Moore's professional activities which are grouped into the following categories: Conferences - General, American Society of Biological Chemists, Federation of American Societies for Experimental Biology, International Congress of Biochemistry, Rockefeller University, and Vanderbilt University.
  - Travel
    - Maps, Austria (Box 102, Folder 841)
    - Maps, Belgium (Box 102, Folder 842)
    - Maps, Denmark (Box 102, Folder 843)
    - Maps, England (Box 102, Folder 844)
    - Maps, France (Box 102, Folder 845)
    - Maps, Germany (Box 103, Folder 846)
    - Maps, India (Box 103, Folder 847)
    - Maps, Italy (Box 103, Folder 848)
    - Maps, Japan (Box 103, Folder 849)
    - Maps, Sweden (Box 103, Folder 850)
    - Maps, Switzerland (Box 103, Folder 851)
    - Maps, United States (Box 103, Folder 852)
    - Maps, USSR (Box 103, Folder 853)
    - Cambridge, England, 1949 (Box 103, Folder 854)
    - European Trip, 1949 (Box 103, Folder 855)
    - Brussels, 1950-1951 (Box 103, Folder 856)
    - Europe, 1950-1951 (Box 104, Folder 857)
    - Cambridge, 1951 (Box 104, Folder 858)
    - Paris, 1952 (Box 104, Folder 859)
    - Europe, 1954 (Box 104, Folder 860)
    - Europe, 1955 (Box 104, Folder 861)
    - Europe, 1957 (Box 104, Folder 862)
    - Europe, 1958 (Box 104, Folder 863)
    - American Chemical Society (ACS) Tour, 1959 (Box 104, Folder 864)
    - Europe, 1959 (Box 104, Folder 865)
    - USSR, 1959 (Box 104, Folder 866)
    - Europe and USSR, 1961 (Box 105, Folder 867)
    - West Coast, 1961 (Box 105, Folder 868)
    - India and Japan, 1963 (Box 105, Folder 869)
    - Marseille, Berlin, London, Paris, 1964 (Box 105, Folder 870)
    - Paris and Cambridge, 1964 (Box 105, Folder 871)
    - Australia, 1965 (Box 105, Folder 872)
    - California, 1965 (Box 106, Folder 873)
    - Paris, 1965 (Box 106, Folder 874)
    - California, 1966 (Box 106, Folder 875)
    - England and Belgium, 1966 (Box 106, Folder 876)
    - Japan, 1967 (Box 106, Folder 877)
    - Seattle, 1967 (Box 106, Folder 878)
    - Tennessee and Texas, 1967 (Box 106, Folder 879)
    - Wisconsin, 1967 (Box 106, Folder 880)
    - California, 1968 (Box 106, Folder 881)
    - Michigan State, 1968 (Box 106, Folder 882)
    - Oklahoma City, 1968 (Box 106, Folder 883)
    - Spinco, 1968 (Box 106, Folder 884)
    - Vanderbilt, 1968 (Box 106, Folder 885, Box 107, Folder 886A, Folder 886)
    - Berkeley, 1969 (Box 107, Folder 887)
    - Canada, 1969 (Box 107, Folder 888)
    - Europe, 1969 (Box 107, Folder 889)
    - Miami, 1969 (Box 107, Folder 890)
    - Michigan State University, 1969 (Box 107, Folder 891)
    - California, 1970 (Box 107, Folder 892)
    - Europe, 1970 (Box 107, Folder 893)
    - Tennessee, 1971 (Box 107, Folder 894)
    - Europe, 1972 (Box 108, Folder 895)
    - Texas and Tennessee, 1972 (Box 108, Folder 896)
    - Europe, 1973 (Box 108, Folder 897)
    - Vanderbilt, 1973-1975 (Box 108, Folder 898)
    - Albany, 1974 (Box 108, Folder 899)
    - Berkeley, 1974 (Box 108, Folder 900)
    - Boston and Rockefeller University Seminar, 1974 (Box 108, Folder 901)
    - Chicago, 1974 (Box 108, Folder 902)
    - Los Angeles, 1974 (Box 108, Folder 903)
    - Palo Alto, 1974 (Box 108, Folder 904)
    - Seattle, 1974 (Box 108, Folder 905)
    - Tennessee, 1974 (Box 108, Folder 906)
    - West Coast, 1974 (Box 108, Folder 907)
    - Wisconsin, 1974 (Box 109, Folder 908)
    - Europe, 1975 (Box 109, Folder 909)
    - NIH [National Institutes of Health], 1975 (Box 109, Folder 910)
    - Vanderbilt, 1975 (Box 109, Folder 911)
    - California, 1976 (Box 109, Folder 912)
    - China, 1976 (Box 109, Folder 914, Folder 913)
    - Germany and USSR, 1976 (Box 110, Folder 915)
    - Moscow, 1976 (Box 110, Folder 916)
    - Notre Dame, 1976 (Box 110, Folder 917)
    - Oklahoma and Nebraska, 1976 (Box 110, Folder 918)
    - Penn State, 1976 (Box 110, Folder 919)
    - Riga, 1976 (Box 110, Folder 920)